[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dental caries, commonly known as a cavity, is one of the most common health disorders, second only to this one.", "correct_answer": "Cold", "incorrect_answers": ["Mumps", "Fever", "Sore throat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Turkeys like to roost high in trees at night.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Plastids are major cell organelles found in which of these groups of organisms?", "correct_answer": "Plants and algae", "incorrect_answers": ["Algae", "Plants", "Plants and animals"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When playing Blackjack in a casino, there are two proper ways to announce your decision after you\u2019ve received a card \u2013 either say it aloud or use some of the commonly accepted non-verbal signs.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is one of the earliest cultivated foods. The protein in these nuts is very much like the protein in human breast milk. This makes it suitable for inclusion in baby foods.", "correct_answer": "Almonds", "incorrect_answers": ["Walnuts", "Peanuts", "Chestnuts"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital and largest city of Austria?", "correct_answer": "Vienna", "incorrect_answers": ["Canberra", "Sydney", "Stockholm"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Komodo Dragon is venomous.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Almonds possess cholesterol-lowering properties.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This organ contains many bacteria, which begin to digest surrounding organs immediately after death.", "correct_answer": "Intestines", "incorrect_answers": ["Liver", "Stomach", "Rectum"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which plane is the first  jet fighter?", "correct_answer": "Heinkel He 280", "incorrect_answers": ["Messerschmidt  M29", "F-117A", "MiG 12"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many engines does a B-52 Bomber have?", "correct_answer": "8", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "4", "6"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Men are considered to be dwarfs in stature if their height is below 130 cm.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]